C

PRIYANKA PANDEY

preyanca1july@gmail.com



UI Designer

Hamburg, Germany



linkedin.com/in/priyanka-pandey-78160337

<u>nka-pandey-78160337</u>

ABOUT

I am a UI designer and I create intuitive user interfaces using Figma and Adobe XD. I started my career as a fashion designer and worked with multiple export houses as a fashion and graphic designer. My background in fashion design equipped me with skills that helped me in a seamless transition to UX and UI design, such as a keen eye for aesthetics, understanding of user preferences, creative problem-solving approach and past experience in Adobe tool suite.

EDUCATION

Careerfoundry

UI Design 2023

NIFT, New Delhi

Fashion Clothing and technology 2011

DDU Gorakhpur, University

Master's in clothing and textile 2008

LANGUAGE

- English
- Hindi

UI SKILLS

- Wireframing
- Prototyping
- Typography
- Iconography
- · Graphic design
- Style guides
- · Design systems
- Employer branding
- Logos
- Infographics
- 3-D mockups

TOOLS

- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- Canya
- Procreate
- · Corel draw

SOFT SKILLS

- Empathy
- Active Listening
- Interpersonal Communication
- Creative Problem-Solving
- Collaboration
- Easily Adaptable
- Organization

UI DESIGN PROJECTS

Dream Clothing, Responsive Clothing App | Career foundry case study, July 2023

- Designed 20+ high-fidelity screens for iOS and Android platforms, mockups, prototypes, and a comprehensive style guide based on stakeholder requests and end-user feedback.
- Emulated the Design-Thinking process to concept and create solutions for a completely original app.
- Designed and digitally created illustrations in Procreate to **enhance the overall end user experience** while navigating the app.

Heathy Kitchen, Responsive Recipe App | Career foundry case study, August 2023

- Designed **34+ high-fidelity** screens and prototypes by following a **user-centered design process and mobile-first** approach to design a responsive web app for finding and sharing recipes.
- Enhanced app navigation by effectively using advanced filtering and sorting in recipe Search screens.
- Conducted competitive analyses, user interviews, surveys, and A/B testing to gather invaluable research data and develop personas, user flows, and sitemaps.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer, Digital Marketing & Branding | Multiple Brands, 2020-2021

• Boosted digital marketing campaigns by creating more than **100+** graphics (presentations, posts, flyers and brand pages) for social media.

Graphic Designer, Design & Illustration | NonProfit & Freelance, 2015-2017

- Created presentation for Paris Fashion Week for a NonProfit org.
- Created vector graphics for Garment prints for a start up to kick start their journey.
- Created presentation for forecasting upcoming design trends.

Fashion Designer, NCDPD-Govt Of India & Export Houses | 2012-2014

- Designed the complete line of product ranges and collections for clients such as Ikea, Target and Maison Du Monde.
- Designed product catalog and presentations for trade fair such as Maison & Objet Fair Paris and Heimtextil, Frankfurt.
- Managed all phases of product development ranging from design and conceptualization, market research, forecasting to material and fabric selection, pattern making and sample construction.